# Raphael Larrinaga, ux & ui & front end in Brussels

I'm improving my skills at building interfaces since 2012, a lot with Drupal. I work on goal-oriented websites, with the people who needs them, creating prototypes then making them alive with HTML & CSS. Not to impress, not for shiny moving stuff but to solve users needs.

#### Education

Since 2012

Frontend United 2013, 2017, 2018 & Drupal Camp 2014, 2015, 2016, 2017

June 2011

Haute École Albert Jacquard - Namur

Bachelor's degree in Computer Graphics - Web Design & Multimedia

June 2007

Collège Saint-Stanislas - Mons General CESS

#### Tools

Code GIT, VSCode, Sublime text, iTerm, Fractal, Lando, Vagrant, Virtualbox

Ux/Ui Sketch, Adobe Ps Ai Xd, Bootstrap, GA/tag manager, Pen & paper

#### **Interests**

Food, Nature, SciFi, Architecture, Cycling, Sport

https://raphael-larrinaga.be/

https://www.drupal.org/u/raphael-larrinaga

https://www.linkedin.com/in/raphael-larrinaga-252935117

### Experience

02/2019 - now

Walking Men - Digital design agency

Front end development

11/2011 - 01/2019

Tilt Factory - Communication agency

Front end development, web design, Drupal theming

01/2011 - 03/2011

Central Design - UX/UI agency

Web design, front end integration (intern)

# Skills

Frontend Dev HTML, CSS, SCSS, BEM, SMACSS, JS (ES5, ES6, React), PHP, Preprocessing (Grunt, Gulp), Bash, Living styleguide, Mailing

Ux/Ui design IA, Wireframing, Prototyping, Personas, Interface design, Ergonomics, Icon design

Drupal D8, D7, Drush, Composer, Twig, YML, Theming, Site building, Modules dev, Maintenance

### Languages

French Mother language Spanish Father language

English Good written/spoken,

technical



Born in 1988

0485/990.961

Living in Brussels

raphael.larrinaga@gmail.com

Belgian

https://twitter.com/RaphLarrinaga